<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

	<string name="help_quick_start">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Welcome to <i>SPLITS</i></h1>
<h1>Quick Start</h1>
<p>1. Select <b><i>Preferences</i></b> from the upper right hand corner dropdown menu. Select either <b><i>Swim Meet</i></b> or <b><i>Track Meet</i></b>. Swim Meet is the default.</p>
<p>2. Open the <i>SPLITS</i> navigation drawer by swiping the screen from left edge to right or tapping the <i>SPLITS</i> stopwatch icon on the action bar.</p>
<p>3. Navigate to the Athletes screen and add the athletes you want to time.</p>
<p>4. Navigate to the Meets screen and add meet title(s).</p>
<p>5. Navigate to the Individual Races or Relay Races screen. Select the meet, event, and athletes to time from their respective dropdown button lists. Press the <b><i>Start</i></b> button to begin the race; the <b><i>Split</i></b> button to record race splits; and the <b><i>Stop</i></b> button to end the race.</p>
<p>6. After the race is finished, press either the <b><i>Checkmark</i></b> in the action bar or your device’s  <b><i>Back Button</i></b> to prepare for next race.</p>
<p>7. Help is available from the upper right hand corner dropdown menu.</p>
]]>
	</string>
	<string name="help_individual_races">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Help: Individual Races</h1>
<p>1. Select the meet, event, and athletes to time from their respective dropdown button lists.</p>
<p>2. One or two athletes may be timed in any individual race event.
<p>3. Press a <b><i>Start</i></b> button to begin the race; the <b><i>Split</i></b> button to record race splits; and the <b><i>Stop</i></b> button to end the race.</p>
<p>4. To add additional meet, event, or athletes long press its dropdown button or select the applicable screen from the navigation drawer.</p>
<p>5. After race is finished press either the <b><i>Checkmark</i></b> in the action bar or your device’s <b><i>Back Button</i></b> to prepare for next race.</p>
]]>
	</string>
	<string name="help_relay_races">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Help: Relay Races</h1>
<p>1. Select the meet, event, and athletes to time from their respective dropdown button lists.</p>
<p>2. Press the <b><i>Start</i></b> button to begin the relay race; the <b><i>Split</i></b> button to record relay splits; and the <b><i>Stop</i></b> button to end the relay.</p>
<p>3. To add additional meet, event, or athletes long press its dropdown button or select the applicable screen from the navigation drawer.</p>
<p>4. After race is finished, press either the <b><i>Checkmark</i></b> in the action bar or your device’s <b><i>Back Button</i></b> to prepare for next relay race.</p>
]]>
	</string>
	<string name="help_results_best_times">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Help: Best Times</h1>
<p>1. Select an athlete from the dropdown button list.</p>
<p>2. Select <b><i>Individual Event</i></b> or <b><i>Relay</i></b>.</p>
<p>3. Press on an event to see race splits.</p>
<p>4. Email times from the upper right hand corner dropdown menu.</p>
]]>
	</string>
	<string name="help_results_all_races">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Help: All Races</h1>
<p>1. Select an athlete from the dropdown button list.</p>
<p>2. Select <b><i>Individual Event</i></b> or <b><i>Relay</i></b>.</p>
<p>3. Press on an event to see race splits.</p>
<p>4. Email times from the upper right hand corner dropdown menu.</p>
]]>
	</string>
	<string name="help_race_and_relay_splits">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Help: Race and Relay Splits</h1>
<p>1. Press <b><i>edit icon</i></b> to correct or set official race time.</p>
<p>2. Press <b><i>delete icon</i></b> to delete race.</p>
<p>3. Email times from the upper right hand corner dropdown menu.</p>
]]>
	</string>
	<string name="help_athletes">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Help: Athletes</h1>
<p>1. Press the <b><i>Add Person icon</i></b> to add athletes from your contacts.</p>
<p>2. Press the<b><i>Add icon</i></b> to enter an athlete’s name not in contacts.</p>
<p>3. Checked athletes are shown in dropdown button lists; unchecked athletes are hidden from dropdown button lists.</p>
<p>4. Long press on an athlete to edit or delete an athlete’s name. It is not recommended to delete athletes; rather uncheck them instead. Note: When revising an athlete’s name, no changes are made in your device’s contacts. </p>
<p>5. Press on an athlete’s image to show the athlete’s contact information.</p>
]]>
	</string>
	<string name="help_meets">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Help: Meets</h1>
<p>1. Type the meet title then press <b><i>Add Meet</i></b> button.</p>
<p>2. Checked meets are shown in dropdown button lists; unchecked meets are hidden from dropdown button lists.</p>
<p>3. Long press on a meet to edit or delete the meet. It is not recommended to delete meets; rather uncheck them instead.</p>
]]>
	</string>
	<string name="help_events">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Help: Events</h1>
<p>1. This screen is pre-populated with common swim and track meet events.</p>
<p>2. Checked events are shown in dropdown button lists; unchecked events are hidden from dropdown button lists.</p>
<p>3. Long press on an event to edit or delete the event. It is not recommended to delete events; rather uncheck them instead.</p>
<p>4. Pressing the <b><i>+ icon</i></b> checks all events. Pressing the <b><i>- icon</i></b> unchecks all events.</p>
]]>
	</string>
	<string name="help_creat_events">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Help: Create Events</h1>
<p>1. Fill in all required data.</p>
<p>2. Press the <b><i>Create Event</i></b> button.</p>
]]>
	</string>
	<string name="help_FAQ">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Help: FAQ</h1>
<p><b><i>1. How do I add athletes?</i></b> Navigate to the Athletes screen via the navigation drawer or by long pressing on one of the athlete dropdown buttons. Then press either the <b><i>Add Person icon</i></b> to add athletes from your contacts or press <b><i>Add icon</i></b> to enter an athlete’s name that is not in your contacts. </p> <p>Note: if you use the <b><i>Add icon</i></b> you will be given the choice to add the athlete to your contacts. Other than that <i>SPLITS</i> makes no changes to your contact’s information.</p>

<p><b><i>2. Can I add an event if it was not included in the pre-populated list?</i></b> Yes. Navigate to the Create Events screen via the navigation drawer. Fill in the required information and then press the <b><i>Create Event</i></b> button.

<p><b><i>3. There are several pre-populated events that I’ll never use. Is there a way to hide them so they are not visible in the dropdown button lists?</i></b> Yes. Navigate to the Events screen and uncheck all the events that you want to hide. You can also hide athletes and meets is a similar manner.</p>

<p><b><i>4. How do I delete or edit athletes, meets, and events?</i></b> Navigate to the applicable screen, then long press on the item that you want to edit or delete.</p><p> Note: it is not recommended to delete these items, rather uncheck them so they are not displayed in the dropdown button lists.</p>

<p><b><i>5. What do I do if I’ve started a race and there is a false start?</i></b> While the race is running, press either the <b><i>Checkmark</i></b> in the action bar or your device’s <b><i>Back Button</i></b>. This will stop the race and nothing will be saved.</p><p> If you have already pressed the stop button, navigate to a Results screen and press the race you want to delete. This opens the race’s Splits screen. From there you can delete the race.</p>

<p><b><i>6. Can I adjust a race’s final time?</i></b> Yes. Navigate to a Results screen and press on a race to open its Splits screen. From there you can delete the race or edit its time. Editing a race’s time also adjusts each of its splits.</p>
]]>
	</string>

</resources>