<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

	<string-array name="helpActivity_tabs">
		<item>Quick Start</item>
		<item>FAQ</item>
		<item>Preferences</item>
		<item>Setup</item>
		<item>Individual Races</item>
		<item>Relays Races</item>
		<item>Results</item>
	</string-array>

	<string name="help_quick_start">
<![CDATA[
<p><b>Welcome to Splits … an app that times and records swim and track meet events. Follow the following six steps to get started.</b></p>
<p><b><i>1. Enter athlete names and contact information.</i></b> Start by entering all athletes you plan to track into your Contacts. (i.e. use the Google Peoples app to enter your athlete’s name and contact information.)</p>
<p><b><i>2. Select the type of meet you’ll be timing.</i></b> From the Individual Races View (the app’s starting screen), select Preferences from the dropdown menu, select Meet Type, then choose either Swim Meet or Track Meet. Swim Meet is the app’s starting default.</p>
<p><b><i>3. Add athletes and enter the meet name.</i></b> Navigate to the Setup View either from the drop down menu or by long pressing an Athlete drop down button.</p>
<p>&emsp;a) From the Athletes tab add the athletes you plan to track. Note: Splits makes no changes to your contact’s information.</p>
<p>&emsp;b) From the Meets Tab type in one or more meet names.</p>
<p>&emsp;c) Press the <i>back button</i> to take you back to the Individual Races View.</p>
<p><b><i>4. Select the meet, event, and athlete(s).</i></b> From the drop down buttons select the meet, event, and athlete(s) you want to time. You can time one or two athletes for a given race event.</p>
<p><b><i>5. Start the race.</i></b> Press either Start button to start a race. Press the applicable Split button(s) to record the athlete’s splits, and the Stop button(s) to end the athlete’s race. Split times of less than 5 seconds are inhibited to avoid creating unintended splits if a button is double clicked. On some devices the applicable action is initiated upon <i>releasing</i> the button.</p>
<p><b><i>6. Reset to prepare for the next race.</i></b> After completing a race, press the <i>Checkmark</i> in the action bar to prepare for the next race.</p>
]]>
	</string>
	<string name="help_FAQ">
<![CDATA[
<p><b><i>1. How do I add athletes?</i></b> The Splits app uses your device’s contacts, so add all athletes you plan to track into your Contacts (i.e. Use the Google Peoples app to enter your athlete’s name and contact information.) Next, navigate to the Setup View either from the drop down menu or by making a long press on one of the athlete drop down buttons. From the Athletes tab add the athletes that you plan to track. Note: Splits makes no changes to your contact’s information.</p>
<p><b><i>2. How do I add an events? or meets?</i></b> Navigate to the Setup View either from the drop down menu or by making a long pressing on an event or meet drop down button. From the applicable tab you can add, delete, or edit the event or meet titles.</p>
<p><b><i>3. What do I do if I’ve started a race and there is a false start?</i></b> While the race is running, press the <i>Checkmark</i> in the action bar. This will stop the race and any splits will not be saved. If you have already stopped the race, navigate to the Results View and press on the race you want to delete. This opens the Splits View. From there you can delete the race.</p>
<p><b><i>4. What do I do if I can’t find an athlete, event, or meet in the one of the  drop down buttons?</i></b> Long press the drop down button to navigate to the Setup View where you can then select the items (by placing a checkmark in the item’s box). Selected items populate the drop down buttons.</p>
<p><b><i>5. How do I remove athletes, events, or meets from the drop down buttons?</i></b> Long press the drop down button to navigate to the Setup View where you can then deselect items (by removing the checkmark in the item’s box). Deselected items are not shown in the drop down buttons.</p>
<p><b><i>6. Can I adjust a race’s time after I’ve stopped the race?</i></b> Yes. Navigate to the Results View and press on a race to open its Splits View. From there you can delete the race or edit its time. Editing a race’s time also adjusts each of its splits.</p>
]]>
	</string>
	<string name="help_preferences_view">
<![CDATA[
<p>From the Preferences menu you can select the meet type: Swim Meet or Track Meet.</p>
<p>You may also select the option to “Reset athletes on clearing race.” With this option checked, when a race is reset by pressing 
the <i>Checkmark</i> in the Action Bar (Individual Races or Relay Races Views) the athletes will also be reset to “No 
Athlete.”</p>

<p>You can select Splits Preferences from the drop down menu from Individual Races, Relay Races, or Setup Views.</p>
]]>
	</string>
	<string name="help_setup_view">
<![CDATA[
<p>From the Setup View you can add, edit, delete, and select athletes, meets, and events. Selected items (by placing a checkmark in the item’s box) populate the Split app’s drop down buttons.</p>
<p><b><i>Athletes Tab.</i></b> Pressing the add <i>Athlete Icon</i> in the Action Bar will bring up a list of your contacts. Select any contact to add an athlete to the Splits app. Note: Splits makes no changes to your contacts. Tapping on the Athlete’s picture will bring up that Athlete’s contact information.</p>
<p><b><i>Meets Tab.</i></b> Enter a new Meet Title, then press <i>Add Meet</i> to add the meet title to the Splits app database.</p>
<p><b><i>Events Tab.</i></b> The Splits app database is pre-populated with the most common swim and track meet events.</p>
<p><b><i>Create Events Tab.</i></b> This is where you can create an event. Check the box if this event will be a relay. Then enter the event’s distance, distance units (Yard or Meter), style (Back, Breast, Fly, Free for swimming events, or Dash or Run for track meets). Enter the event’s lap distance. As you enter this information you will see the new event’s title being composed. When complete, press <i>Create Event</i>.</p>
<p><b><i>Selecting Items.</i></b> Place a checkmark by an Athlete, Meet, or Event to select the item. Selected items are displayed in the various Splits app’s drop down buttons. Removing the checkmark excludes that item in their respective drop down buttons. For example, if you have no interest in seeing swimming events that are in meters, uncheck all of the meter events.</p>
<p><b><i>Editing and Deleting Items.</i></b> Long pressing any item under the Athletes, Meets, or Event tabs brings up the edit mode (red background) of the respective tab. Press the <i>Edit Icon</i> or <i>Delete Icon</i> to edit or delete the selected item. Generally you should deselect an item rather than deleting it.</p>
<p><b><i>Navigation.</i></b> Swipe either right or left, or press a tab to navigate among the the tabs. Note: swiping the tab titles in the Action bar displays any hidden tabs. From the dropdown menu, you may navigate to the Preferences or this Help View.</p> 
]]>
	</string>
	<string name="help_individual_races_view">
<![CDATA[
<p>The Individual Races View is where you time up to two athletes in an individual event.</p> 
<p><b><i>Select the meet, event, and athlete(s).</i></b> From the drop down buttons select the meet, event, and athlete(s) that you want to time. If you do not see the item you want, long press its drop down button to navigate to the Setup View. From this view select the item that you want or added it. (See Setup View) Press the <i>back button</i> to return to the Individual Races View.</p>
<p><b><i>Start the race.</i></b> Press either <i>Start Button</i> to start a race. Press the applicable <i>Split Button(s)</i> to record the athlete’s splits, and the <i>Stop Button(s)</i> to end the athlete’s race. Split times of less than 5 seconds are inhibited to avoid creating unintended splits if a button is double clicked. On some devices the applicable action is initiated upon <i>releasing</i> the button.</p>
<p><b><i>Reset to prepare for the next race.</i></b> After completing a race, press the <i>Checkmark</i> in the action bar to prepare for the next race.</p>
<p><b><i>Navigation.</i></b> From the dropdown menu, you may navigate to the Results, Relay Races, Setup, Preferences, or this Help View.</p>
]]>
	</string>
	<string name="help_relay_races_view">
<![CDATA[
<p>The Relay Races View is where you time four athletes in a relay event.</p>
<p><b><i>Select the meet, event, and athletes.</i></b> From the drop down buttons select the meet, event, and athletes that you want to time. If you do not see the item you want, long press its drop down button to navigate to the Setup View. Either select the item that you want, or added it. (See Setup View) Press the <i>back button</i> to return the the Relay Races View.</p>
<p><b><i>Start the relay race.</i></b> Press the <i>Start Button</i> to start a race. Press the <i>Split Button</i> to record the athletes’ splits, and the Stop button to end the relay race.</p>
<p><b><i>Reset to prepare for the next relay race.</i></b> After completing a relay race, press the <i>Checkmark</i> in the action bar to prepare for the next race.</p>
<p><b><i>Navigation.</i></b> From the dropdown menu, you may navigate to the Results, Individual Races, Setup, Preferences, or this Help View.</p>
]]>
	</string>
	<string name="help_results_views">
<![CDATA[
<p>The Results View is where you view an athlete’s Best Times or All Races results for individual events and relays. Pressing a 
race will open the detailed Splits View. The Splits View shows a race’s splits. From this view you can delete the race or edit its 
time. Editing a race’s final time also adjusts each splits time.</p>
]]>
	</string>

</resources>